Try to conquer the darkness
Try to conquer the darkness, now let us reflect on something
Now let us reflect on something
Granted, the destination is far and the atmosphere is treacherous
Yet we will surely win, yet we will surely win
Just have a little patience, try to conquer the darkness
Stopping briefly to run even faster, stopping briefly to run even faster
Then strive to increase the momentum, try to conquer the darkness
Let us scatter these clouds of despair
Let us scatter these clouds of despair, let us share each other's sorrow
The fog is not so dense, the fog is not so dense
That we won't be able to clear it, that we won't be able to clear it
Just try to give courage to everyone, let us reflect on something
Try to conquer the darkness, now let us reflect on something